Guide to the Nathaniel Gage Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1987-080
  - PC 127 c.l Ed. 350A/Gage and Hess: "An Overview of Process-Product Research on Teaching": Presentation given to Fort Hays State University, 1986 Feb 21 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - PC 127 c.2 Ed. 350A/Gage and Hess: "An Overview of Process-Product Research on Teaching": Presentation given to Fort Hays State University, 1986 Feb 21 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Ed. 350: Editing Notes by R.E. Snow (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Education 350A: Psychological Studies in Education, 1986-87 Autumn (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Ed. 350A, 1986-87 Autumn (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Ed. 350A, 1985-86 Autumn (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Ed. 350A, 1985 Fall (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Ed. 350A, 1984 Fall (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Ed. 350, 1984 Fall (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Ed. 350: Gage and Hess, 1982 Fall (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Ed. 350A: Grading, 1979 Fall (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Ed. 350A, 1979 Autumn (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Ed. 350A: Fall 1979, Midterm Exam 350A, Handout, 1979 Dec 4 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Ed. 350A: Student Information Sheets, 1979 Fall (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Ed. 350A: Notes on Lectures, 1979 Fall (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Ed. 350: Ed. Psychology Text Designs, 1982 Fall (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Ed. 350AB: Class Handouts and Tests (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Ed. 350: Notes of Talk by N.L. Gage and Correspondence, 1981-82 Fall (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Ed. 350B, 1980-81 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Ed. 350A, 1980-81 Fall (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Ed. 350 A and B: Planning, Feedback, etc., 1980-81 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Ed. 350B, c.l Proceedings, 1979-80 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Schedules, Outlines, Exams, Handouts 350A-B, 1979-80 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Ed. 350AB King/Snow/Calfes, 1978-79 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Ed. 350B, 1980 Winter (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Ed. 350B, 1979 Winter (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Ed. 350A, 1979 Autumn (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Ed. 350A, Cranbach Press, 1979 Fall (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Oxford University, 1984- (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Oxford, 1983-84 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous: Oxford Stuff (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - South Carolina Educator Improvement Task Force (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - University of South Florida (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - "What Educators Ought to Know about Research on Teacher": Paper given for the Doctor Residency Seminar, College of Education, University of South Florida, 1985 Nov 12 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - University of Sydney (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Syracuse University (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Teachers College (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Tel Aviv University (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Temple University (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Tennessee Technological University (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Texas Woman's University (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - University of Utah: Michael Gardner, 1986 Oct (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - University of Washington, Seattle, WA (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - AID (Teacher and Teaching Evaluation Project) (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Association of Colleges and Schools of Education in State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Australian Association for Research in Education, Paper Given at Melbourne, Australia, 1979 Oct 10 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Australian Association for Research in Education (AARE) (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Bay Area Teacher Education Seminar (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - James McKeen Cattell Fund (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Center for Research into Practice (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - (University of Illinois): Center for the Study of Reading, Champaign, Illinois (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - NCRIPTAL (National Center for Research to improve Post Secondary Teaching and Learning), Ann Arbor, Michigan: meeting (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Research Council of Canada (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - RION (Research Institut Voor Het Indervigs in Het Noorden) (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Ed. 215: Notes on Course Papers (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Ed. 215: Notes, not yet used (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Ed. 215: Midterm Exam II, 1986-87 Spring (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Ed. 215: Syllabi, 1986-87 Spring (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Ed. 215/Psych. 145, 1986-87 Spring (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Ed. 215/Psych. 145: Student Information Sheets, 1986-87 Spring (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Ed. 215: Second Med. Q. Exam, 1986 Spring (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Ed. 215/Psych. 145: Handouts, 1986 Spring (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Ed. 215/Psych. 145: Syllabus, 1986 Spring (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Ed. 215, 1985-86 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Ed. 215/Psych. 145, 1985 Summer (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Ed. 215, TA Notes, 1985 Summer (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Ed. 215/Psych. 145: Course Description, 1985 Summer (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Ed. 215/Psych. 145, 1984 Summer (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Ed. 215/Psych. 145: Information on Students Sheets (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Ed. 215/Psych. 145, 1983-84 Summer (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Ed. 215/Psych. 145, 1982 Spring (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Ed. 215: Teaching Materials Already Used, 1980 Summer (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Shockley et. al.: A debate on heredity, environment, race, I.Q. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Shockley et. al.: A debate on heredity, environment, race, I.Q. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Educ. 215, Problem Checklists, 1987 Fall (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Educ. 215: Ohio Checklists (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - SUSE: Ed. 215: Transparencies on Educational Objectives (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Teacher Problems Checklists, STTM and Ed. 215 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Test Construction Manuals (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Ed. Psych. Vocabulary (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - SUSE: Educ. 215: Transparencies on Heredity and Environment in I.Q. Differences (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Education 215: Notes on Course Papers (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Educ. 215: Bibliographic Resources (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - SUSE: Directed Reading List (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Ed. 215: California Psychological Inventory, 1976 Spring (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Ed. 215: Midquarter Evaluations, 1976 Spring (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Ed. 215: Student Evaluations, 1975 Spring (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Educ. 215: Transparencies on Paradigms of Teaching (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Grade Change: Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - SUSE: Education 211, 1970 Summer (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Educational 245X: The Education of the Exceptional Child (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Educational 257 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Ed. 289X: STEP, 1984-85 Fall (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Ed. 289X: Reserve Readings, 1985 Fall (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Ed. 289X: Videotapes List (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Ed. 289X: Feedback from Students, 1984 Fall (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Ed. 289X: Outlines, 1984 Fall (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Ed. 289X: Lecture Notes, 1984 Fall (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Ed. 289X: Survey Test, 1984 Fall (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Ed. 289X, 1984 Autumn (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Ed. 289X: Transparencies, 1984 Sep 27 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Ed. 289X: Transparencies, 1984 Oct 2 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Ed. 289X: Transparencies, 1984 Oct 4 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Ed. 289X: Test 3 on Individual Instruction (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Ed. 289X: Test 2 on Individual Instruction (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Ed. 289X: Test 1 on Individual Instruction (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Winegrad Outline on Lecturing (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Ed. 289X: Craig Outline on Lecturing (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - SUSE: STEP: Education 341, Koff and Kline and Description of STEP Program, 1969 Summer (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Ed. 343X: Motivational Processes in Education (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Ed. 349: Professional Education of Teachers, 1983 Spring (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Ed. 349: Professional Education of Teachers, 1982-83 Spring (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - SUSE: CERAS Interim Grant Committee Meeting, 1977 Sep 19 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - CERAS (General), 1977- (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - SUSE: CERAS, 1977- (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - NIE (General), 1982- (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - SCRDT Publications List (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - List of SCRDT and PTE Publications which N.L. Gage has copies of (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Apple Education Foundation (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - PTE, 1981 Dec (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Marianne Amarel (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Mike Atkin (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Edwin Bridges (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Robert N. Bush (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Calfee, Professor Robert (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - SCRDT: Environment for Teaching Program: E. Cohen (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Arthur Coladarci (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Cronbach, L.J. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Larry Cuban (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Eisner, Elliot (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Fisher, Michele (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Edmondo F. Fuenzalida (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Gross, Dr. Richard (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Edward Haertal (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Hanna, Paul (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Hastorf, Albert H. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - SCRDT: R.D. Hess (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Hilfgard, Ernest R. (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Krantz, Susan (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Krumboltz, John D. (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - SCRDT: Levin, Henry M. Low Income 0403 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Litt1eboy, Jeff (Stanford Daily) (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - McLaughlin, Milbrey (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Nell Noddings (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Olkin, Ingram (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Phillips, Denis (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - SCRDT: Low Income Program: Robert Politzer (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - David Rogosa (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Shirlman, Lee (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Skeff, Kelley (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - SCRDT: Richard Snow (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Spindler (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Patrick Suppes (Individual Groups) IV (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - SCRDT: Carl E. Thoreson (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Walker, Decker (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Ed. 317: Information Sheets, 1987 Winter (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Ed. 317, 1986-87 Winter (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Ed. 317: Reprints, 1987 Winter (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Hans Weiler (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Master for Student Information Sheet for Dr. Gage's Classes and Syllabus (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Ed. 317: Represents for Readings, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Ed. 317: Notes, 1986 Winter (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Ed. 317: Final Exam, 1985-86 Winter (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Ed. 317, 1985-86 Winter (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Ed. 317: Student Information Sheets, 1986 Winter (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Ed. 317: Syllabus and Lecture Notes, 1986 Winter (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Ed. 317: T.A. Notes, 1986 Winter (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Ed. 317, 1985 Winter (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Ed. 317, 1984-85 Winter (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Ed. 317: Framingham Study Shows How Added Factors Multiply Risk; Original and Tables 1, 2, 3 and Figure 1, 1985 Winter (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Ed. 317: Spaulding Handouts, 1985 Winter (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Ed. 317: Rogosa Papers, 1985 Winter (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Ed. 317: Borg and Ascione Papers, 1985 Winter (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Ed. 317: Bourtie Handouts and Appendices, 1985 Winter (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Ed. 317: Mid Quarter Exam, 1985 Winter (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Ed. 317: "Question Pool" etc., 1985 Winter (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Ed. 317: Handouts, 1983 Winter (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Ed. 317: Outlines of Handouts, 1983 Winter (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Ed. 317: Quizzes, 1983 Winter (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Ed. 317: Student Questionnaires, 1983 Winter (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Ed. 317: Syllabus and Student Grades, 1983 Winter (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Ed. 317: Grades, 1981-82 Fall (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Ed. 317: Notes, 1981 Fall (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Ed. 317: Redfield, Davis L. and Rousseau, Elaine Waldman, A Meta-Analysis of Experimental Research on Teacher Questioning Behavior, 1981 Fall (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Ed. 317:, 1981-82 Fall (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Ed. 317: Miscellaneous, 1981 Fall (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Ed. 317: Readings on Ethnography, 1981 Fall (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Ed. 317: Literature Cited, 1981 Fall (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Ed. 317: Notes for Today, 1981 Fall (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Ed. 317: Readings on Bennett, 1981 Fall (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Bar-On, Ehod and Perlberg, Arye: The Facet Approach in Developing a Theory of Instruction (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Blackwell, Laird: Aptitude Treatment... (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Block, J.H. (Ed.) Mastery Learning: Theory and Practice, Chapter 1 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Block, J.H. (Ed.) Mastery Learning: Theory and Practice, Chapter 1 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) Copy 2 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Block, J.H. (Ed.) Mastery Learning: Theory and Practice, Chapter 4 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Block, J.H. (Ed.) Mastery Learning: Theory and Practice, Chapter 4 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) Copy 2 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Block, J.H. (Ed.) Mastery Learning: Theory and Practice, Chapter 5 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Block, J.H. (Ed.) Mastery Learning: Theory and Practice, Chapter 5 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) Copy 2 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Borg, W.R. "The minicourse as a vehicle for changing teacher behavior: A three-year follow-up" (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Borg, W.R. "The minicourse as a vehicle for changing teacher behavior: A three-year follow-up" (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) Copy 2 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Borg, W.R., Kelley, M.L., Langer P., and Gall, M. "A minicourse: A microteaching approach to teacher education" Chapter 1 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Borg, W.R., Kelley, M.L., Langer P., and Gall, M. "A minicourse: A microteaching approach to teacher education" Chapter 1 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) Copy 2 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Borg, W.R., Kelley, M.L., Langer P., and Gall, M. "A minicourse: A microteaching approach to teacher education" Chapter 2 (Gage, Ed 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Borg, W.R., Kelley, M.L., Langer P., and Gall, M. "A minicourse: A microteaching approach to teacher education" Chapter 2 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) Copy 2 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Costin F., Grenagh, W.T. and Menges, R.J.: "Student ratings of college teaching: Reliability, validity, and usefulness" (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Costin F., Grenagh, W.T. and Menges, R.J.: "Student ratings of college teaching: Reliability, validity, and usefulness" (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) Copy 2 (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Gage, N.L., "Teaching Methods" (Gage, Ed. 217, 24-hour res.) (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Gage, N.L., "Teaching Methods" (Gage, Ed. 217, 24-hour res.) Copy 2 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Greene, David: Teachers attributions .... (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - McLeish, J. The Lecture Method, pp. 32-48 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - McLeish, J. The Lecture Method, pp. 32-48 (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) copy 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Mischel, W. Construction of Personality (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mischel et al article: "Cognitive and Attentional Mechanisms in Delay of Gratification" (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Peterson, Penelope: "A Review of the Research on Mastery-Learning Strategies" (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Peterson, Penelope: "A Review of the Research on Mastery-Learning Strategies" Copy 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Peterson, Penelope L.: "Teacher Approval and Affective Outcomes" (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Rossi, Robert J.: "Selling and Buying: Suggestions for Research on Teaching and Learning" (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ed. 215: Lecture Notes, 1985 Summer (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Huber, M.: "Is the Adjustment ... " (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Keller, F.S. "Good-bye Teacher ... " Journal of Applied Behavior Analysis, No.1, (24-hour res. for Gage's Ed. 317, Introduction to Research on Teaching), 1968 Spring (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Keller, F.S. "Good-bye Teacher ... " Journal of Applied Behavior Analysis, No.1, (24-hour res. for Gage's Ed. 317, Introduction to Research on Teaching) Copy 2, 1968 Spring (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Kent, L.: "Student Evaluation of Teaching" (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Martin, J.R. "Can there be a universally applicable criteria of good teaching?" (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Martin, J.R. "Can there be a universally applicable criteria of good teaching?" (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) Copy 2 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Martin, J.R. "Can there be a universally applicable criteria of good teaching?" (Gage, Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) Copy 3 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - McCleish, J. "The Lecture Method" pp 1-17 (Gage Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - McCleish, J. "The Lecture Method" pp 1-17 (Gage Ed. 317, 24-hour res.) Copy 2 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Teaching and Teacher Education: an International Journal of Research and Studies, Accession ARCH-1990-021
  - Moscow conversations, 1985 Oct (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes letter from Michael Dunkin
  - TATE 4, 1986-89 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, memos, and minutes of editorial board
  - TATE 3, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, of Gage, Michael J. Dunkin, and others
  - TATE, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, memos, and minutes of editorial board; a few articles
  - TATE USSR trip 1985, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Correspondence (Gage and Dunkin mostly), notes, copies of travel documents
  - TATE origins (2), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Correspondence (Gage and Dunkin mostly), memos, and notes
  - TATE mailing lists (1), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - TATE: International Association for Research and Teaching: correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - TATE: International Associations: correspondence, misc. programs, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH 1992-048
  - American Educational Research Association, 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, papers
  - AERA (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AERA Division K Program Papers (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Newsletters, correspondence, paper proposals
  - American Psychological Association Division 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Newsletters
  - APA Meeting, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, program
  - APA, 1989-90 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, newsletters
  - APA, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - APA Division 8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - APA Division 15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cardelle, Maria (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, clippings
  - Center for the Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences: Expenses, Year End Report, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, rosters
  - De Landsheere, Gilbert (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, articles
  - Dillon, James T. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, c.v.
  - Dornbusch, Sanford (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Correspondence
  - Drew, Pam (Box 1, Folder 15)
    ms. draft
  - Elementary School Journal (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - European Association for Research on Learning and Instruction (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Call for papers
  - Feger, Hubert (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Giaconia, Rose (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gleser, Leon (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Grawemeyer Award (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Greeno, J. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Research proposal
  - Hofer, Manfred (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, paper, article
  - Hunsen, Thorsten (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, paper, reprints
  - India (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Promotional mailing
  - International Congress of Psychology (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Conference materials
  - Israel (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, conference materials
  - Janesick, Valerie (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Jensen, Arthur R. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kelly, Eamonn (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, letters of recommendation
  - Knight, Stephanie L. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Letter of recommendation, C.V., articles
  - Maxwell, Robert (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Miller, Allan (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, interview
  - Miscellaneous 3 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1989 Apr 11- (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Morine-Dershimer, Greta (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Education, Meeting, 1991 Fall (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Mailings, roster, program
  - National Academy of Education, Meeting, 1989 Fall (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, mailings, roster
  - National Academy of Education, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Conference mailings
  - National Academy of Education, 1987-88 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Memos, conference mailings
  - National Association for Secondary School Principals (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - National Society for the Study of Education (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Membership mailings
  - New York Times (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, article
  - O'Loughlin, Michael (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Correspondance, C.V., papers, article for grant review
  - Pergamon Press (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Correspondance, book proposal
  - Pergamon (Various) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - National Academy of Education #5 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, newsletter, article
  - National Academy of Education #4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Correspondance, newsletters, memos
  - National Academy of Education #3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Correspondance, memos, papers, notes
  - National Academy of Education #2, Programatic Organizations (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Education #1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, newsletters, conference materials
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Letter
  - National Assessment of Educational Progress (Programatic Organizations (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Publication list
  - Programatic Organizations California Round Table on Educational Opportunity (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Institute of Education (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, memos, notes
  - Swedish National Board of Universities and Colleges (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Seminar program
  - Teacher Education and Computer Center, Santa Clara County (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Memo, brochure
  - Office for Educational Research and Improvement U.S. Department of Education (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Adenubi, Mobolaji (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Boruch, Robert (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, papers, reprints
  - Branca, Nicholas A. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Memo
  - Browning, Carol (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Byers, Joe (East Lansing) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Note
  - Carroll, John B. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Charters, W. W. Jr. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Chatterjee, B. B. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Clark, Richard (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Coates, Tom (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Dissertation proposal
  - Crocker, Robert K. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Austin, Gilbert (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - SCRDT: Dell, Daryl L. IIC (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Deterline, William A. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Duke, Daniel Linden (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Article
  - Falus, Dr. Ivan (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, reprint, journals
  - Glasser, Robert (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Gliessman, Dr. David (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - SCRDT: Harlow, Bruce (Editor) lID (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Havers, Norbert (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, booklet
  - Hayes, R. B. (Feedback Research) (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Project proposal
  - SCRDT: Hudgins, Bryce (Postdoctoral Fellow) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Jackson, P. W. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Janesick, Valerie (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Memo, paper
  - SCRDT: Pat Jones (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Klotz, Gunter (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - SCRDT: Koff, Robert (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Correspondence, papers, article
  - Landa, Lev (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Correpondence, booklet
  - Larrivee, Barbara (Box 5, Folder 18)
    letter, research project proposal
  - E. McDaniels, Purdue University (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Letter, note
  - Menges, Robert (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Parker, Edwin B. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Perlberg, Dr. Arye (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Pidgeon, Douglas, A. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Rappaport, Dr. Chanan (Jerusalem, Israel) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Rosenshine, Barak #1, 1968 Jan-1970 Aug (Box 6, Folder 3)